zmenu.com 2019-03-20

# The most comprehensive restaurant menus & dish reviews site - Zmenu

Privacy Policy

Welcome to ZMenu (“we,” “us,” “our,” or “ZMenu”), the complete photo menu that helps you find delicious food with confidence. Your (“you,” “your”) privacy is important to us at ZMenu, Inc.  In this privacy policy, we want to explain the following topics in details.  

  * What information we collect and how we use them

  * How we share your information

  * How we protect your information

  * Your choices about your information

  * Other websites and services

  * Changes to the privacy policy

By using ZMenu website (ZMenu.com), mobile applications and all associated services, features and content (“Service” or “Services”), you acknowledge that 

  * You have read and accept the practices and policies described in this Privacy Policy.

  * You are over 13 years of age. 

    * ZMenu does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for this Service. This service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13. 

    * If you believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, please let us know at support@zmenu.com and we will verify, terminate the account and delete all account information as soon as possible.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that ZMenu does not own or control (including any third-party products or services used for logging into the Service or that are integrated with the Service), or to individuals that ZMenu does not employ or manage.

##  Private info

To provide and continuously improve the quality of our service, we may collect the following types of information:

  * Private Profile Information: In order to take advantage of certain ZMenu features and enable us to contact you for the purposes described above, you can optionally create a ZMenu account (your “Account”) by providing an email address and creating a password or by logging in using a third party service such as Facebook (your “Account Information”). If you log in using a third party service such as Facebook, the email address that you used to register with that third party service may be used to create your Account, and a password unique to ZMenu may be generated for you, which you can change at any time. Passwords are stored using industry standard methods. Your actual password is never stored or visible to ZMenu, its agents or employees at any time. Your email address will never be displayed to other users of the Service,unless you choose to include it in your public profile.

  * Your Email address: ZMenu will use your email only to send communications directly from or related to the Service, such as:

    * Occasional announcements about product updates or improvements.

    * Notifications when others interact with you or your public content on ZMenu.

    * Recommended content from ZMenu that we think might be interesting to you.

    * User feedback or survey.

    * Food-related offers, rewards or recommendations from ZMenu.

    * Contest-related communications if you participate in a contest or promotion hosted by ZMenu or by a third party using the ZMenu platform to host a contest or promotion.

    * Notices when we make material changes to our Privacy Policy or Terms of Service.

    * Personal messages related to the Service, your use of the Service or our Terms of Service.

  * Third Party Connections: To enable features such as “Find Friends” or “Sharing” on ZMenu, you can connect to third party services (such as Facebook and Twitter) using the secure, industry standard connection methods provided by these third parties. When you make a connection between your ZMenu account and one of these third party services, the third party service may share certain information about you with ZMenu.  These third parties never reveal your passwords to us and are responsible for informing you about what information they will share with ZMenu. We will never post content to your third party services unless you’ve explicitly chosen to enable us to do so.

  * Payment Information: We do not directly collect or store any payment information at this time, but may use third party services such as PayPal or Goodsie to enable you to purchase ZMenu-related products or services. These Terms of Service do not cover third parties’ handling of Personal Information, so if you use these third party services, be sure to review their terms of service and privacy policies.

  * Your Current Location: In order to find nearby content and receive targeted information, you can opt into sharing your mobile device or web browser’s location.

If you choose not to provide us with any of the information above, you may not be able to take advantage of certain features.

##  The information you choose to share publicly

  * Public Profile Information: When registering or after registering, you can optionally enter in other public profile information such as a profile photo, public display name, city, website and so on. 

  * Public Content: 

    * Photos: You can upload dish photos to ZMenu. These photos will be shared publicly on ZMenu per our Terms of Service. When you upload a photo, any associated metadata your camera might have embedded into that photo, such as the date taken or place taken, may be uploaded as well.

    * Other types of Content: You can create other types of content, such as reviews, ratings, tags and bookmarks, which may be displayed publicly along with associated metadata such as date and time created.

    * If you remove any information that you posted to the Service publicly, copies may still remain viewable in cached or archived pages of the service. These copies won’t disappear until the caches are cleared or the archived pages are deleted or expired.

##  Technical and Usage Information 

In order to diagnose and improve our service, we also automatically receive, and log certain types of technical and usage information either using our own technology or third party analytical tools. This type of information includes:

  * Technical information about your browser and mobile device.  This type of information is used in diagnosing and prioritizing bug fixes issues.  This type of information is only used internally for analytics purpose in an anonymized way.

  * Usage information, such as pages you request, searches you conduct and the features and emails from ZMenu that you interact with. This type of information is only used internally for analytics purpose in an anonymized way.

  * IP address, cookies and other similar technology: These information help us to distinguish between unique browsers and devices to prevent ZMenu from displaying duplicate experience to you. For instance, we use these technology to

    * Keep you logged into ZMenu so that you don’t have to log in again every time you close your browser.

    * Remember the last location you entered on ZMenu so that you don’t have to enter your location again and again.

    * Display each type of announcements only once.

    * Remember certain preferences you might set.

  * Crashes and error reports: If you encounter a crash or error while using our Service, we may generate a crash report that includes technical, usage and, if you are logged in, your Account information so that we can diagnose and potentially prevent the problem in the future.

  * ZMenu uses Google Analytics and NewRelic  to collect the above information.

    * You can read about Google Analytics' Privacy Practices here:

    * You can read NewRelic's Privacy Policy here:

The public information you choose to share will be always and only be used in accordance to our Terms Of Service ([www.ZMenu.com/terms](http://www.zmenu.com/terms).jsp) . 

Your non-public information will not be shared with third parties, except in the following scenarios:

  * Agents, Including Employees, Contractors and Service Providers: To provide great service, we employ the services of individuals (such as employees, contractors and lawyers) and companies (such as consultants and service providers such as a push notification delivery service) to perform tasks on our behalf. These agents will only use the minimal set of Personal Information necessary to provide service to you.

  * Change of Control: In the event that all or a substantial portion of the assets, business or stock of ZMenu are acquired by, merged with or transferred to another party, or in the event that ZMenu goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, your information would be one of the assets that is transferred to or acquired by the third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of ZMenu or its assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

  * Legal requests and protecting ZMenu: We may disclose information about you to third parties if we have a good faith belief that such a disclosure is reasonably necessary to (i) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (ii) enforce or apply our Terms and Privacy Policy; (iii) comply with legal process or other government inquiry, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us; or (iv) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. Information we share about you may be accessed, processed and retained for an extended period of time when it is the subject of a legal request or obligation, governmental investigation or investigations concerning possible violations of our terms, policies or to prevent harm.

We will not share your Personal Information with the following parties without your explicit consent:

  * Partners and Advertisers: While we may provide aggregate usage and demographic information to partners and advertisers to help them understand our audience and target their communications accordingly, we will not directly share any personal-identifiable information with partners or advertisers. The aggregated usage and demographic info we shared, and any information you directly shared with any third party, is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners and is not subject to our control.

  * Contests by Third Parties: Third parties may host contests and sweepstakes using ZMenu in accordance with our Terms of Service. We cannot be responsible for information you provide directly to third parties, via the Service or otherwise, however we will not provide your email address to third parties without your consent, which you may provide by choosing to enter such a promotion, in accordance with the promotion rules. ZMenu may send contest-related communications directly to you on a third party’s behalf.

Personal Information is transmitted to and stored by ZMenu using industry-standard methods for each type of information. Our databases and servers are protected from unauthorized access using modern security and authentication methods such as passwords and access keys.

No method of transmitting or storing data can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, however. While we try our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee that it will never be viewed, tampered with or intercepted by an unauthorized third party. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of your Personal Information.

We will notify you by email as long as we have reason to believe that your Personal Information has been compromised due to a security breach or used in an unauthorized manner, but by using this Service, you agree to release us from any and all claims arising out of unauthorized use of your information.

The Service contains links to third party websites and mobile applications. ZMenu is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of third parties. When navigating to another site you should read the privacy policy stated on that site.  This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Service.

Please do your part to help us. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique account and password information, and for controlling access to emails between you and ZMenu, at all times. 

  * You can access, modify and correct any information of yours any time. 

  * You can opt out of any marketing communication from ZMenu by unsubscribing via the link included in the email. You may not opt out Service-related communications (e.g. account verification, order confirmation and so on)

  * You can choose to disable cookies via settings in your browser(s).

  * You can choose to not share your current location.

  * You can choose to upload photos as “anonymous user”. The photo will be credit to “anonymous user” in public, but the Service will still associate this photo with you in order to display it in your profile and will only be visible to you.

If you do not wish to have your Personal Information used or shared as described in this document, please discontinue use of the ZMenu Service or do not provide such information.You can choose to delete your account by email us at [support@zmenu.com](mailto:support@zmenu.com). Please use “Account Deletion Request” as the title of such request. Note that after you delete your account, the photos you uploaded will still be stored in the system, but will be credit to “Anonymous user”.  

We are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites or services linked to or from our Service, including the information or content contained within them. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Service to another website or service, our Privacy Policy does not apply to those third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that third party's own rules and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and do not have control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or service and you allow them to access your User Content at your own risk.

ZMenu reserves the right to modify the Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of these Terms will be posted on the Service. If you access or use the Service, you agree accept the Privacy Policy effective at the time of your access to or use of the Service. You should revisit this Privacy Policy on a regular basis as revised versions will be binding on you. Any such modification will be effective upon our posting of new Privacy Policy. We will include the date of the last revision of the Privacy Policy. 

If you still have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or your Personal Information, please contact us feedback@zmenu.com.
